iqelite.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy | IQ Elite

## We ♥ your **privacy**. 

At IQ Elite, we respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of any personal data we collect. The purpose of our **Privacy Commitment** is to clearly state our dedication to you in maintaining privacy and confidentiality of sensitive data. 

Here are some of the questions that you might like to have answered. 

### How is my data used? 

Great question! The information gathered about you when you register with IQ Elite and subscribe to our Services is used to offer you our different Services. All precautions have been taken on our databases to archive your information in a secure environment. Only a small number of our employees have access to your information, which is only accessible in case of necessity. 

Here's how we use collected information: 

  * To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
  * To personalize your experience: We may use information to understand how you, as a group, use our functions and features on our Site. 
  * To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 
  * To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send updates. We may also contact you this way to respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. 
  * We may occasionally send you promotional offers from some of our partners. If you do not wish to receive any special offers from IQ Elite or our partner companies, you may unsubscribe from this kind of emails (category "Other") on http://www.iqelite.com/account/notifications/ 

### What is this 'data'? 

Another great question! Glad you asked. Any personal information from your profile, messages on your chats or even your Facebook profile is what we mean by 'private data'.   
We would never: 

  * publish private chats 
  * sell Facebook content 
  * sell your pictures or personal information 

All your data belongs to you and it stays that way! 

### How do you collect my information? 

All the information we receive about you, actually comes from you! This is either information filled out by yourself or by integrating your facebook into your profile. You control how much you wish to share with us. You can always refuse to provide us and other members with personal information, however this may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

### How do you protect my information? 

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and any other data stored on our Site. 

### Who’s going to get my information? 

Like we said before, no one will be getting their hands on your information! Not even your mother! And don't worry about receiving any spam emails, our email lists are safe and secure. **We are as careful and concerned about your privacy as you are.**

### How do I to stop receiving emails from you in the future? 

If you feel the notifications we send you start to become a bit more than you had expected, feel free to edit your Email Notifications. However we recommend that you don't unsubscribe from all our newsletters. We would like to know how you are doing and to keep you updated about our latest development. 

### What if I email you guys? 

Contact us?! We'd be delighted!! Our customer support would be honoured, ecstatic and privileged to receive any emails from you regarding any questions or feedback, and will get back to you ASAP.   
Contact us at: IQ Elite Customer Support. Remember what happens between you and customer support, stays that way. 100% confidentiality. If you still have additional questions about our Privacy Commitment, please check out our FAQs or directly contact us: IQ Elite Customer Support.

### What if a member is very persistent? 

We want to keep a tight check on the quality of members on the website and will restrict access or even remove accounts that have been reported with a valid complaint. If a member persists to harass you, block them and feel free to report them to us. We will ensure you remain anonymous if you choose to do this. 

### Do you use cookies? 

We aren't talking about those kinds of cookies! We are talking about internet cookies, a small text file that is stored on your computer to record previously filled in data. Pretty cool right? And not at all dangerous. Cookies are used to deliver content and information that is specific to your interests, profile and for the administration of passwords and other settings. They are not linked to your personal data but rather they enable us to recall specific data and content every time you return to the IQ Elite saving you valuable time.   
You can of course disable your web browsers from accepting cookies, however this will restrict certain sections of our website to you. We would be very disappointed if you were not able to experience everything we have to offer.   
Here is more information we have provided on the use of cookies. 

### Finally, 

By using our site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If there is anything that you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site.   
We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, this is one reason we have decided to share with you our **Privacy Commitment**.We believe that the internet has been humanity’s greatest accomplishment thus far. For us, the Internet was created to promote communication, interaction and a means to connect people from all corners of the world, not just looking at cat pictures.   
However people are misusing and stealing data provided by others. We strongly recommend that you are careful with the information you share. Have a look at some of our safety tips.   
If you still have additional questions about our Privacy Commitment, please check out our FAQs or directly contact us: IQ Elite Customer Support.

This document was last updated on July 23, 2013 

We ♥ your **privacy**.
